Ronald Jimenez

1845 Wisteria Ln, Carson City, NV, 67890 RJJimenez@newmail.co (345) 678-9012

Trained computer engineer with extensive experience in network, server, and security protocols.

Thorough understanding of hardware and software and how they can affect local, campus, and wide area network productivity. Provided remote support for staff and students and collaborated with several technical teams to improve network functionality.

Key Skills

- CompTIA Network+_r August 2017
- Work extensively with TCP/IP, IPX/SPX, Ethernet (10/100/1000) and NetBIOS technologies
- Windows Active Directory, Linux, and Novell Netware
- Cisco Certified Network
 Professional (CCNP), July 2018

Professional Experience

Network Specialist

UNLV Lee Business School, Las Vegas, NV j January 2020 - Present

- Develop application solutions for senior staff to seamlessly access the school network
- Provide and implement network solutions to protect the school from ransomware attacks
- Contribute to the technical development of network solutions for the entire UNLV campuses
- Give comprehensive presentations about network health to the Dean, Provost, and associated staff

IT Technician

UNLV Lee Business School, Las Vegas, NV j December 2018 - November 2019

- Maintained and configured Cisco LAN/CAN/WAN and provided basic help desk support across associated campuses
- · Troubleshooting computers for faculty and staff
- Selected for team that expanded the school's Wi-Fi offerings to faculty, staff, and students

Education

Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering

University Of Nevada, Las Vegas, Las Vegas, NV Jan 2015 - December 2019